其实 我曾经历过的最独特的驾驶体验之一
Alright so one of the most unique motoring experiences I've ever had
是在
personally was back
那时我每天都是开特斯拉
when I was daily driving a Tesla I got to drive
还借来了2008年的特斯拉跑车
and borrow the original the Tesla Roadster from 2008
真正体验到电动跑车的起源
and got to really feel the beginning
以及原本电动跑车应该有的感觉
and the experience of what original electric sports car was supposed to be
而且也能够清楚地看到此后的演变
and then obviously see the evolution that happened since then.
现在 我每天开的车是911
Now you know I'm daily driving a 911
我不禁想问
and The question I may have had is
那样的怀旧体验会是什么样的呢？
what would an equivalent throwback experience be?
不过这个车 看上去可没那么简单
And this one, it's actually not exactly what it looks like
你可能会想 哦
because you're probably thinking, oh
你是说你要开手动的老款涡轮增压车？
you're going to drive a manual OG turbo?
那可是辆疯得不可思议的车
That's a crazy car to drive.
不是 不是 不是 不是 不是！
No, no, no, no, no.
这辆车是电动的
This one, this one's electric.
这几天
So for the past couple of days
迈尔斯和我开这辆车真的太享受了
Miles and I have had a real treat driving around this thing.
这是款改造过的964代保时捷911
This is a sort of remodeled 964 generation Porsche 911.
这车是由一家名为Sacrilege Motors的公司完全电动化
to be fully electric by a company called Sacrilege Motors
名字也是不无讽刺
probably appropriately named
因为很多人看到这个会有反应
because there's plenty of people who see this
看到电动的车 大家可能觉得有点不妥
and see electric and that feels sacrilegious
但接着你会看到评论
but then you see the reviews
以及人们对这辆车的驾驶体验评价
and what people have thought about driving this thing
看起来他们确实做得相当出色
and Seems like they've done an incredible job.
所以我特别想试一试
So I just wanted to check it out
看看这辆车的实际驾驶感受
and see how this actually drove.
结果证明 这是一种将手动原味与全新动力系统完美结合的体验
And it turns out it's an incredible combination of the manual original feel
与全新动力系统相结合
with this obviously new powertrain being
我想说 这个真的比原版要好
Well, I'll say it, better than the original.
回去看看
Now, if you go back and watch
原版《与2008年特斯拉跑车同住》的视频
that original Living with the 2008 Tesla Roadster video,
你会发现
you'll see, I mean
与今天的特斯拉相比 真相差甚远
it's quite a throwback from the Teslas of today.
屏幕明显小了很多
The screens are much smaller
车身也小了许多
the car is much smaller
电池的体积也缩小了很多
the battery is much smaller
各方面的发展都显得落后得多
and everything is just further behind.
这款车更加类比 虽然不是完全如此
It's more analog, but not completely.
这一代车型最早是在80年代推出的
This generation car first came out in the 80s.
这是一款1989年的经典车型
It's a 1989 model.
所以这里是没有屏幕的
And so there were no screens.
这真是更加怀旧的感觉
This is even more of a throwback.
所以你可能会觉得 跟它一起生活挺疯狂的
And so you might think living with it would be crazy.
然后拿其中一辆稀有的车
And then taking one of these rare cars
把它改造成电动汽车
and going through the work of turning it into an electric car
简直是个疯狂的主意
is just a crazy idea.
不过我和它一起生活一段时间后
But after I've lived with it now
我明白为什么大多数人会这么做
I actually get why people do it.
在我的体验中 会有一些惊喜
And there may be some surprises in my experience
现在我来跟大家分享
that I'll share with you now.
那我们就直接进入正题吧
So let's just jump right in.
首先 这辆车真是太美丽了
So first of all, gorgeous car.
我可能有点偏见 因为显而易见
I might be biased because I'm obviously
我选择了这款深受启发的车
I chose a car that's inspired heavily by this
其实我也有一辆黑色的车
and I actually have a black one too
但你可以看到这是宽体车型
but you can see this is the wide body one
而且它还是一款敞篷车 也可以称作敞篷版
and it's a convertible as well so cabriolet if you want to call it that
有趣的地方
and the thing to note here
很多部件都是共享的
that's kind of interesting is there's a lot of parts
这些部件是从原版保时捷上共享的
here that are shared from the original Porsche parts
但也有许多新部件 比如这些轮子
but also a lot of new parts like you can see these wheels here
你可以看到这些新的Brembo刹车 基本上快放不下轮子了
you also see these new Brembo brakes that barely fit underneath the wheels
不过他们装上了Pilot Sport轮胎
and but they get in there pilot sport tires
几乎放不下
that barely fit under the fenders
后面的轮胎也很宽
and these are some big wide tires back here too
说实话 这些是295宽的18英寸轮圈
matter of fact what can i see these are 295 section 18 inch rims
后面的轮胎非常出色
these are some juicy tires back here
能匹配这辆车的动力
for the amount of power this thing puts out
这款车的输出功率为500马力和500牛米
which is 500 horsepower and 500 newton meters
现在 它是电动车
Now, it's electric
所以现在很多新车的电池都
so a lot of the cars built today have the batteries in
像一个小滑板一样 安装在车底
like this little skateboard underneath the car.
那么 这里的电池在哪里呢？
But where's the battery in here?
实际上这里有两个电池
There's actually two.
一个在前面
Big one in the front
另一个在后面
and big one in the back.
如果有机会的话
so on the off chance
你在进行自驾游的时候
that you're doing a road trip
在这辆车里 你还是有一点前备厢空间
or something in this car you do have a little bit of front trunk space
虽然不多
not a huge amount
但足以放一个适配器 或者一个小手提包
but enough for an adapter maybe a bag a carry-on size bag or so
而那半个电池就藏在地毯下
but that's half the battery right there
此外还有可调节的减震器
below that carpeting also your adjustable dampers
我想那是你的挡风玻璃清洗液 正是在这里
and i i think that's uh your windshield wiper fluid so there's
一半的重量就藏在这个标志性的鸭尾后面
where half the weight goes So behind this iconic ducktail
而电池的另一半则位于旧发动机的位置
where the old power plant used to be there's the other half of the battery
还有你的减震器 当然
and of course your dampers as well
不过 这真的很重 现在你能看到
but that is a whole bunch of weight so now you can see
重心分布得相当均匀 这里就没有储物空间了
it's kind of evenly distributed there's no more storage in here
前后各有一半的电池
but there's half the battery in the front half the battery in the back
一次充电大约可以行驶200英里
And in total, that's going to get you around 200 miles
of range on a single charge
如果你正常驾驶的话
if you drive it like normal
这其实很令人印象深刻
which is actually kind of impressive
毕竟 这车真的很小
because of how small this car really is.
我想 你不会指望它有很多放电池的空间
I mean, you don't expect a whole bunch of space to put battery in.
不过 因为电池不在底部
But since the battery is not on the floor
这就意味着驾驶位置
that means the driving position
内饰方面与原版的相似度比以往更高
and all this interior is closer than ever to the original.
这些是新的座椅
These are new seats.
不过 当然
But then, of course
我刚进来时
when I get in here
你将会看到大量原汁原味的保时捷 真让我想起了以前
you're going to see a whole bunch original Porsche so I remember
我之前拍过一段关于最新电动大众巴士的视频
when I made that video on the refreshed Volkswagen bus the electric one
ID Buzz
the ID buzz
很多评论都说这车挺酷的
there was a lot of comments that were like this is kind of cool
我觉得
I guess
我希望他们能复刻那个老款复古设计
but I wish they just took the exact old retro design
然后把它做成电动车
and they just made that one electric
现在我完全明白了
and I totally get it now
因为这辆车基本就是这样
because that's basically what this car is
我周围全是传统部件 没有任何屏幕
I am surrounded by analog parts not a single screen in sight
其实这里只给了我一个小屏幕 用于车载系统
well actually they've given me a little tiny screen here for car play
这根本不算是真正的屏幕
and it barely counts as a screen
因为这是额外配置的
because this is added extra
但开车时 你只需专注于方向盘
but when you're driving you're focused here on this wheel
还有这精致的内饰
and on this beautiful interior
现在它几乎就是你的仪表了 你之前见过的那个钥匙
which is basically just your gauges now you saw that key from before
这是启动汽车的方法 把钥匙直接放进去转动就可以了
this is the way to turn the car on stick the key right in there turn it
你会看到这些仪表转动 因此它们的显示变得更新了
and you see these gauges spin up so the gauges are of
这些仪表当然也进行了更新 以适应这辆车的电动特性
course updated a bit to work with the electric nature of this car
所以它在显示我的电池电量
so it's telling me my battery level
它还会告诉我一些其他信息
It's also going to tell me
我现在选的是什么驾驶模式
which drive mode I'm in
我现在使用了多少电量
how much power I'm using.
音效真的很棒
Great sound.
你可以看到我还剩下多少续航距离
You can see how much range I have left.
我现在是在悠闲模式
I'm in chill mode right now.
而那边显示的是我的速度
And over there is my speed.
这是一个更新的仪表盘 但保留了传统的模拟风格
So this is an updated gauge cluster, but very much analog.
这里是你的手刹
You've got your parking brake down here.
我现在把脚放在刹车上 准备倒车、行驶和切换空档
This is, I'll put foot on the brake, reverse, drive, neutral.
他们还新增了一个MagSafe电源接口
And they've actually added a MagSafe puck with power
便于为你的MagSafe设备充电
just to charge your MagSafe devices.
如果你想用CarPlay
So if you do want CarPlay
想把你的iPhone放在那儿的话
if you want to put your iPhone there
这是一项很不错的细节设计
that is a nice little touch that they've added.
虽然这辆车的其他部分都特别复古
Even though the entire rest of this car is super retro
你的新手机可以在这里充电 正好合适
you can have your brand new phone charging right there where it belongs.
不过
but
嗯
yeah
哎呀 这里的一切都让我感到无比怀旧
oh my god every single little thing happening here is such a throwback
空调的通风口就在这里 用于冷却
the air conditioning these notches here for cooling
加热也在这里 显然都是手动通风口
and heating for where the air comes out obviously all manual vents
这类功能我们不使用任何屏幕
we're not doing any screens for that type of stuff
当然 这里有锁
and of course you have your lock here
打开门的方法就在这个小装置
and the way you open the door is just this little thing right here
这真太棒了 我太喜欢了！
this is sick I'm loving it.
现在这里还有几个按钮
Now there's a couple other buttons over here
你最好了解一下
that you do want to know about,
特别是这个有感叹号的按钮
specifically this one with an exclamation point on it
这会把车切换到运动驾驶模式
which switches the car from chill mode
等一下 显示屏上写着‘启动我’
hold on it says crank me
因为它希望我将模式从舒适切换到运动
because it wants me to fully turn it on, from chill mode to sport mode.
而这些车的特点就是非常定制
And The thing about these cars is they are so kind of custom
几乎每一辆都是独一无二的
and like one-off built
你知道 舒适模式的再生制动效果更强
that you know there is chill mode which is more regen
再生效果可以达到65% 功率大约是三分之二至四分之三
65% regen and a you know two-thirds three-quarters of the power
但它们可以进行个性化调整
but they can tailor it
他们在为你定制汽车时 会完全按照你的要求来
when they build you the car to be exactly the way you want
运动模式的再生制动效果较低 大约在20%左右
sport mode has less regen closer to 20% regen
运动模式会再次提供全部动力 可以根据需要定制
but is giving you all of the power again all that can be customized
坐在这样的车里 感觉真是不可思议
but it's just crazy to me to sit in a car like this
而且能想到以前的汽车是那么小
and knowing that cars used to be so small
那时你只需伸手就能过去
that you could reach over
伸手就能碰到另一边 根本不用伸直手臂
and just Touch the other side without fully extending your arm
以前的汽车小得多
cars used to be so much smaller
薄得多 这车竟然没有安全气囊
so much thinner There's no airbag in this car
不过这里还是有雨刷的
but you've got your windshield wipers here.
这里还有转向灯
You've got your blinkers over here
所有东西依然在熟悉的位置上 感觉真亲切
Things are all still in the familiar places
这让我感到满满的怀旧情怀
but it's just such a throwback.
这真是太赞了！
It's so sick.
这是一种独特的体验 后座也很重要
This is This is a one-of-a-kind Experience you also have your back seats.
别忘了这些细节
Don't forget about those
我的车也有这个设计 但是几乎没法用
and My car has the same thing, barely usable.
后面不适合成年人坐
You don't want an adult back there
不过 如果你愿意的话 坐一下也可以
but you could do it if you want to.
不过 我要把驾驶体验交给迈尔斯了
But I'm going to pass it to Miles for the driving experience
因为我已经给你看过车内了
because I've shown you the interior.
我已经给你讲了基本的情况
I've shown you the basics.
你能开200英里 那迈尔斯
You get 200 miles of driving, so Miles
开起来感觉怎么样？
what's it like to drive?
这款车的品牌叫Sacrilege Motors
The brand of this car is Sacrilege Motors
因为对许多老派保时捷爱好者来说 这样的想法
because the idea to a lot of OG Porsche enthusiasts
有人会把这样的车改成电动
that someone would take a car like this
装上电动机 听起来有点疯狂 对吧？
and put electric motors inside is kind of crazy, right?
我觉得汽车圈其实有个大问题
And I think there's this big problem with the car community
人们认为车辆只需要分成两种
where people think it just has to be one
或是另一种类型
or the other for certain types of vehicles.
大家都觉得新的法拉利超级跑车用V6而不是V12令人失望
People are upset that the new Ferrari hypercar has a V6 instead of a V12.
不过 如果你买得起那辆车
But if you can afford that car
又有什么理由不去收藏12辆V12的车呢？
what's stopping you from owning 12 other cars with a V12?
你应该以同样的视角来看待这辆车
You should look at this car the same way.
如果你有接近80万美元
If you have nearly $800,000
或者花更多钱来买这样的车
or more to spend on a car like this
那还有什么能阻止你花同样的钱买一辆经典的
what's also stopping you from spending the equivalent money on a classic
保时捷911呢？
ICE Porsche 911?
考虑到这些情况
And so with all that in mind
我觉得这点很重要
I think it's important
我们应该避免把这与内燃机911进行比较
that we don't try to compare this to an ICE 911
因为如果你能买得起这辆车
because if you can afford this car
你也可以选择买一辆内燃机964
you can also just get an internal combustion engine 964.
但我想说的是 他们在这方面确实做得很出色
But what I will say... is that what they've done an amazing job at
开这款车时 唯一让你感受不到911的 可能就是它的电动动力系统
with this car is making sure the only thing that doesn't feel like a 911
就是它的动力系统是电动马达
is the fact that you have electric motors for the drivetrain.
开这车的其他每一个方面
Literally every other aspect of driving this car
甚至连气味
even down to the smells
都是你在经典保时捷911上能感受到的
is definitely what you would experience with a classic Porsche 911.
方向盘手感出色 沉稳、连接紧密 反馈非常到位
The steering field is nice, weighted, connected, super communicative.
让它动起来需要一些力气
takes a bit of elbow work to get it going
就像90年代和80年代的经典保时捷那样
just like a classic Porsche from the 90s, 80s.
明显地 它的底盘非常低
It's obviously super low to the ground.
车身非常稳固
It's very stiff
因为它配备了可调的三向悬挂
because of those three-way adjustable coilovers
稍后我们会详细讨论
that we'll talk about a little bit later.
接下来我们来说说它的轻盈感
And then the lightness.
这辆车的重量刚刚超过3000磅
This car only weighs just barely over 3,000 pounds
这使得它比市面上大多数燃油车轻得多
which makes this lighter than most gas powered cars
（未提供对应内容）
currently on sale today.
我们依然保持着传统911的4060重量分配
We also still have the 4060 weight distribution of a traditional 911.
因此 重量转移、整体平衡和操控性都相当出色
So weight transfer, general balance and handling
这些表现与原版车相当
it's all on par with the original car.
当然
But then of course
这款车配备了超过500马力和500牛顿米的扭矩
you've got 500 horsepower, just a little over 500 Newton meters of torque.
我会把这里转换成磅尺
I'll put the conversion here to pound feet.
这辆车重3000磅 马力有500 并且仅为后驱
And so 3000 pounds, 500 horsepower and rear-wheel drive only.
这辆车相当快
This thing is quick
坦白说 有时候开起来让人有点害怕
and it's quite frankly a little scary at times
就是因为它的体积很小
just because of how small it is.
这车确实有种老派车的感觉
It certainly has that OG car feel
就像我们今年频道里介绍的其他车
just like other cars we've had on the channel this year,
比如大众ID Buzz
like the Volkswagen ID Buzz.
这种老车真的让人觉得
Older cars like that really make you feel like,
是的 如果你在开这车的时候出错
yeah, if you screw up in this thing
很难有其他东西能救你
there's not a lot that's going to save you.
不过 这正是开这样的车的乐趣所在
But that's a part of the fun with cars like these,
这些老式保时捷 以及这些专为运动打造的跑车
these older Porsches, these older purpose-built sports cars.
在某种程度上 缺乏安全感
the lack of safety in a sense
反而增添了驾驶的刺激体验
is almost what adds to the thrill of the experience
在这辆车里 根本没有任何辅助系统
and so in this car there are zero nannies
牵引力控制也没有
you have no traction control system
你把方向盘向左打
so you turn the wheel to the left
猛踩油门 车子就开始侧滑
and floor it and you are going sideways
这辆车的悬挂系统真的很特别
the suspension on this car is actually really interesting
首先 你肯定注意到这段视频里 它的悬挂很硬
firstly i'm sure you've noticed in this footage that it is pretty stiff
车身也很低
uh it sits very low
所以你会感觉到很多颠簸的路面
and so you're gonna feel a lot of those bumps
这要看个人情况 还是能接受
but It's certainly livable depending on who you are, I guess
还有你生活的地方
and the area you live in.
我住在新泽西
I live in New Jersey
所以显然  这里的乘坐舒适性不算很好
so obviously ride comfort is going to always not be the best
和其他地方比
compared to other places.
但是它是可以调节的
But it is adjustable
这是因为这些三段可调避震系统
and that's because these are three-way adjustable coilovers
由佩斯基赛车制造
made by Penske Racing.
他们因提供卓越的调教而闻名
And they're known for making setups for, like, you know,
超级跑车和运动跑车
supercars, sports cars.
那么这个调校到底是什么呢
And so what this setup is
这实际上与GT3 RS中使用的配置非常相似
is very similar to something that you'd get in, like, a GT3 RS,
例如
for example.
这个设置的一大亮点是配备了远程油液箱
One of the killer parts of this setup is having remote reservoirs
打开车后备箱 就能看到远程油液箱
that you can see by opening the rear hatch of the car.
这些远程油液箱连接着
And so you have these remote reservoirs that are connected to
车底的主油箱
the primary fluid tank underneath the car
通过这些液压管线 油液可在两个油箱之间循环
via these hydraulic lines that are feeding fluid back and forth.
所以 首先能得到的好处是更方便维护
and so the benefits you're getting is firstly maintenance
只需打开后备箱 就能轻松接触到这些油液箱
it's easier to access those reservoirs by just popping over the rear hatch
而且 您可以轻松调节
but then secondly you're getting easy adjustability
只需打开后舱盖
by just opening the rear hatch
然后调整与储液箱连接的旋钮
and adjusting the knobs connected to the reservoir
这让您可以轻松适应自己的驾驶体验
which makes it super easy to tailor your driving experience
以适应不同的情况
to whatever scenario you're in
这并不是专为超高性能赛道
this is not necessarily designed to be a super high performance
而设计
track vehicle
但由于这种配置
but because of this setup
还有车的重量和动力
and the weight and the power
您完全可以带这辆车去参加赛道活动
you certainly could take this to a track day
而且可能会让不少人感到尴尬
and probably embarrass a lot of folks.
总体来说 这款车的乘坐舒适性不仅优于原版964
And so overall, you're working with ride comfort that's not only better
这个部分的意思在中文中未体现
than what you would
而且还有更高的可调性和能力
get from an original 964, but more adjustable and more capable as well.
这辆车的刹车系统也相当出色
You're also working with a very healthy brake setup in this car.
前面装有六活塞刹车钳 后面则是四活塞刹车钳
You've got six piston calipers up front, four piston calipers in the rear,
四轮都配备了大型Brembo钢制刹车盘
big steel Brembo rotors all around.
这样的配置可谓
And so a setup like that is what you'd find
许多高端超跑的标配
on a lot of like high-end supercars
近十年来的超跑普遍都采用这种配置
from like the past 10 years or so.
不过 这款车的刹车调节很出色
But the braking modulation is also really nice.
刹车也不是特别敏感
It's not super grabby
也不会像很多运动汽车那样突然刹车
and stabby like a lot of sports cars are known to be.
刹车非常平稳 渐渐地停止
It's very smooth and gradual
这使得它作为日常代步车更容易适应
which makes it a lot easier to live with as a daily driver
如果这是你想尝试的
if that's something you wanted to attempt to do.
就像我一开始提到的
So like I mentioned at the beginning
我觉得没有必要把它拿来和
I don't think it makes sense to try to compare this
这款车与同时期的911比较也没有意义
as an alternative to the equivalent 911 from this era.
但即便如此
But even with that in mind
我认为我们应该比较一下乐趣与这一时代911的关系
I do think we should evaluate the fun factor versus a 911 of this era
没有电动机和电池作为动力
not powered by electric motors and a battery.
这完全取决于你是谁
I think it really depends on who you are.
对某些人来说 没有那种声音是无所谓的
For some people, not having that noise is just not going to do
无所谓的
anything for you,
无论这辆车多么吓人和强大
no matter how scary and how capable the car is overall.
我想 这是我会为某人买的
To me, this is something I think I would love to buy for someone
他想体验驾驶911的感觉
who wants the feeling of driving a 911
却不想承担维护的烦恼
without having to deal with all of the maintenance responsibilities
维护这款时代的911所需的麻烦
that come with maintaining a 911 from this era.
买这款车的时候
When getting a car like this
你就不必操心那些事了
you're not going to have to deal with that sort of stuff.
我觉得了解这款车也是一个有趣的挑战
And I think it's also an interesting challenge to try to learn
去理解这种瞬间动力输出的汽车
and understand a car with this type of instantaneous power delivery
没有电子牵引控制
without any of the electronic traction control assists
及其他辅助功能
and all that fun stuff.
这与理解
It's certainly different than learning to understand
993涡轮的手动变速器大相径庭
a manual transmission 993 turbo
在驾驶中 你需要合理掌握换挡时机和油门控制
where you have to properly time shifts and throttle input with, you know
如果你驾驶涡轮增压的911 涡轮增压动力反应会明显
the boost of the turbos if you have a turbocharged 911, that sort of stuff.
这绝对是完全不同的体验
It's certainly an entirely different experience
这种体验无法与
one that you can't just compare directly to
传统内燃机的911直接相比
an internal combustion engine powered 911.
在这样的车里 你几乎很难不享受驾驶的乐趣
I think it's pretty hard to not have fun in a car like this
即使你更喜欢8000转的高转速体验
even if you would prefer having, you know, an 8,000 RPM, high revving
但这绝对不能取代手动变速器的魅力
, you know, manual transmission experience.
这完全不是对那种体验的替代
This is not a replacement for that
如果你的预算足够的话
but if you have a budget that allows for it
我觉得这真是个不错的增添
I think it's a pretty cool addition.
我觉得很多人可能会
It's something that I think a lot of people are going to be
对此感到怀疑
naturally very skeptical about
但我觉得应该尝试一下
but I think it's only right
在排除之前 先试试看吧
that you give it a try before ruling it out.
当你拥有这些特性时
When you have all these things
当你拥有保时捷的媒体中心
when you have the Porsche media center
你能感受到保时捷的操控感
you have the Porsche steering feel
你还能闻到保时捷那种独特的香味
you have the Porsche smell
就像我吉姆叔叔那些老保时捷的味道
it smells like a lot of my Uncle Jim's old Porsches.
这真是太疯狂了
It's actually crazy.
考虑到这些事情时
When you put all that into consideration
你就能明白价格为何如此高了
you can understand how you can get to an extremely high price point because
这些都是手工打造的车
these are hand-built machines.
这些可不是特斯拉Model 3
These are not Tesla Model 3s where, you know
你会发现在这里有些奇怪的缝隙
you'll see weird gaps here
以及那里的奇怪不一致
and there and weird quirky inconsistencies.
这确实有着经典德国车的感觉
This has that real OG German car feel, which is, you know
对某些人来说 这种感觉是无法用价格来衡量的
it's hard to put a price on that for some people.
我想我爱上这车了
I think I love this thing.
我觉得我蛮喜欢这个的
这可能是我在这里测试过的最爱车型
This might be my favorite car that we've actually gotten to test here.
这既是车的魅力 也是体验的一部分
And it's part the car, part the experience.
我一直在想那个2008年特斯拉跑车的视频
Again, I keep throwing back to that 2008 Tesla Roadster video
自第一款特斯拉跑车以来 技术进步得令人赞叹
how far the technology has come since the original Tesla Roadster,
比如电池密度
the battery density
续航能力有多强
how much range you get
充电速度有多快
how fast they charge.
我还没给你看呢
I didn't even show you.
结束前 我要给你看最后一件事
I should show you one last thing before I wrap this up.
充电方式其实很简单
How you charge this is actually kind of really intuitive.
只需抓住它 然后拉一下
You just grab this and pull.
这个就可以打开
And this opens.
充电口就在这儿
And there's your charge port right here.
CCS
CCS.
直接把它插进来
Pop it right in there.
就像你想象的 它看起来像个油箱
Like you would expect that to be a sort of a gas tank
但他们想到了所有
but they've thought of everything.
我真的喜欢这个项目
But I love this project
因为这辆车明显是80年代的经典原版
because it's just such an obviously original, OG-looking car from the 80s,
其造型经典
the classic shape.
没人不喜欢这款911的外形
I don't think anyone's ever not liked the shape of this 911
但它有我熟悉的驾驶感觉
but then it just has what I'm familiar with
就是电动驾驶的体验
which is the electric driving experience
而且表现得相当好
and kind of does it really well.
这是一款超级有趣的车
This is an ultimate fun car.
我超级喜欢它！
I love it.
如果你想了解更多 可以点击下面的链接哦
I'll leave a link below if you want to check them out.
看这个视频的人应该都不会买这辆车
Probably nobody who actually watches this is going to go buy one of these
但这真的是太牛了！
but it's one of the sickest things ever
我很开心能体验到这一切
and I'm glad I got to experience it.
希望我能再试一次
Hopefully I get to try this again.
谢谢大家观看！
All right, thanks for watching.
下个视频再见！
Catch you in the next one.
保持联系！
Peace.